Today, the quarter 4 of our company ICICI LBR General
Insurance and Company is coming,
which is coming tomorrow on 15th April. We will
talk about what kind of numbers and what kind of results can be there. Here you will see that there is a
company worth Rs 88000 crores on which there is no debt
and also you will see that there is an
insurance company here but there is no debt on it,
so we got to see this very positive thing.
The stock has a good PE and ROC as per the industry PE.
ROE is slightly lower.
Here we see its book value
near 331.  And its current price is that of
1782.  The company
also pays a small dividend.  Here, if we look at its other
details, then you will see that in
its performance of one year,
this level of 2050 has been seen acting as a strong resistance.
Also, this level of 1850 was
seen acting as a strong support.
But the market crashed and after that this
support also broke and the stock was
seen taking support near its 1700 level.
Talking about the results,
its
profit had decreased in the last quarter.  Net
profit also declined simultaneously.  The
result was negative.  Now
if we talk about how quarter 4 can be, then here you will
see that the sales of the company this year are
increasing as per last year
and its expenses are also increasing
but the company is making profit
even though the margin is low and net profit is also increasing,
so operating profit is increasing,
net profit is increasing, sales are also
increasing, so chances of positive result are
high, positive result can be seen,
that's all in today's video,
like the video, share it, subscribe to the channel,
thank you so much for watching this
video.